iPhone cameras have gone to the point
now where they're essentially more than
enough for making YouTube videos.
There's been more than a few times that
I filmed videos just with my iPhone with
this MagSafe accessory. This is a
portable MagSafe monitor that you can
plug into iPhone and see what's on the
front. So, that means you can fully
utilize the back camera, which is going
to be way better quality. So, I got this
camera a few years ago that is a
expensive DSLR
>> [music]
>> and I've tested it with the latest
iPhones and it's actually kind of scary
how little difference there is. All
right, so this is a DSLR and then this
is the iPhone. I don't think there's a
big difference. I think if I fully
switch to the iPhone, nobody would even
notice. And a lot of times the iPhone is
actually easier because there are no
settings to mess with and you can't
really mess with the recording because
on a on expensive camera, you have a
bunch of settings that you have to learn
how to use. But, if you do make content
or you want to make content, this thing
could help you save thousands of
dollars.